A Christmas Detour is a tv movie, comedy, romance film directed by Ron Oliver.
A bubbly bride-to-be’s Christmas plans take an unexpected turn when her holiday flight to New York
is detoured and she encounters a cynical bar manager who has lost his faith in love.
As she scrambles to make it back east for Christmas—and plan her upcoming wedding—she begins
wondering if she’s marrying the right man, and learns a surprising lesson about love.
Paige Summerland, played by Candace Cameron Bure.
Dylan, played by Paul Greene.
Maxine Harper, played by Sarah Strange.
Frank Harper, played by David James Lewis.
Jack Collins, played by Marcus Rosner.
Bryce, played by Kaj-Erik Eriksen.
This is a list of television films produced for the cable networks
Hallmark Channel (HC) and Hallmark Mystery (HMM).
Such films are currently called Hallmark Channel
Original Movies and Hallmark Mysteries.
The Hallmark Channel was officially launched in August 2001, with its sister channel Hallmark
Movies & Mysteries (originally Hallmark Movie Channel) launched in January 2004.
In addition to stand-alone original films, both channels broadcast a number of original film series, including Garage Sale Mysteries, Jesse
Stone, Signed, Sealed, Delivered, Aurora Teagarden Mysteries and The Good Witch, as well having produced mystery-themed wheel series.
The Hallmark Channel achieved its highest-ever broadcast premiere ratings with the 2014 original movie
Christmas Under Wraps, starring Candace Cameron Bure, which was watched by 5.8 million viewers.
Both networks receive their highest ratings during their "Countdown to Christmas" period, with a
succession of festive original films being broadcast from late October to late December.
A number of these films are also carried in Canada by the W Network and Citytv under content distribution agreements with Hallmark parent
Crown Media; the vast majority of Hallmark Channel films are filmed in Canada and thus qualify for Canadian content quotas.
In the United Kingdom, Hallmark Original Movies are
shown on Movies 24, a sister channel.
The film explores themes of holiday, flight, christmas, bride-to-be.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.